{
    "mcqs": [
        {
            "question": "Which is the best Football Club in England?",
            "correctChoice": "ManchesterUnited",
            "choices": {
                "a": "Liverpool",
                "b": "ManchesterUnited",
                "c": "Arsenal",
                "d": "Chelsea"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is the best Football Club in Spain?",
            "correctChoice": "RealMadrid",
            "choices": {
                "a": "RealMadrid",
                "b": "Barcelona",
                "c": "AtleticoMadrid",
                "d": "Sevilla"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is the best Football Club in Germany?",
            "correctChoice": "BayernMunich",
            "choices": {
                "a": "BayernMunich",
                "b": "Dortmund",
                "c": "Schalke",
                "d": "Leipzig"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is the best Football Club in France?",
            "correctChoice": "PSG",
            "choices": {
                "a": "PSG",
                "b": "Lyon",
                "c": "Monaco",
                "d": "Marseille"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is the best Football Club in Italy?",
            "correctChoice": "ACMilan",
            "choices": {
                "a": "Juventus",
                "b": "ACMilan",
                "c": "Roma",
                "d": "InterMilan"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is the best Football Club in Portugal?",
            "correctChoice": "Sporting",
            "choices": {
                "a": "Benfica",
                "b": "Sporting",
                "c": "Porto",
                "d": "Braga"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is the best Football Club in Netherlands?",
            "correctChoice": "Ajax",
            "choices": {
                "a": "Ajax",
                "b": "Feyenoord",
                "c": "PSV",
                "d": "Alkmaar"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is the best Football Club in USA?",
            "correctChoice": "DCUnited",
            "choices": {
                "a": "DCUnited",
                "b": "Seattle",
                "c": "LAGalaxy",
                "d": "NewYorkCity"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is the best Football Club in Pakistan?",
            "correctChoice": "Spartans",
            "choices": {
                "a": "Spartans",
                "b": "SAGarden",
                "c": "ModelTownFC",
                "d": "Gladiators"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is the best Football Club in Turkey?",
            "correctChoice": "Galatasaray",
            "choices": {
                "a": "Galatasaray",
                "b": "Fenerbache",
                "c": "Besiktas",
                "d": "Istanbul"
            }
        }
    ]
}